<game name="Mario!" author="Benjamin Massey">
  <category name="Historical Facts">
    <clue>Mario’s original name from his debut in the arcade game Donkey Kong.</clue>
    <clue>This game introduces Yoshi as a character.</clue>
    <clue>This Nintendo console featured the first entry in the Mario Kart series.</clue>
    <clue>The creator of Mario.</clue>
    <clue>
      Super Mario Bros. was released on this year for
      the Nintendo Entertainment System (NES).
    </clue>
  </category>

  <category name="Technical Junk">
    <clue>
      While the Nintendo 64 gives away its amount of bits,
      this is the bit number for the Super Nintendo (SNES).
    </clue>
    <clue>
      Super Mario 64 features this gimmick on startup,
      which was made as a technical demo of the Nintendo 64’s
      advanced 3D capabilities.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      The GameCube was named after this animal during its
      development at Nintendo. This name is printed on
      components, and is also the name of a popular
      emulator.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      In Super Mario 64, this boss character shares the same
      audio file as Bowser, only with a differing playback
      speed.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      This graphical technique for the Super Nintendo was
      used by early games like Super Mario Kart to simulate
      3D long before 3D became a truly viable option.
    </clue>
  </category>

  <category name="Koopa the Quick">
    <clue>
      The game version featuring this language is the
      fastest for speedrunning most speedrun categories in
      Super Mario 64.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      During the primary boss battles in Super Mario 64, the
      player must perform this action on Bowser in order to
      defeat him. It is also a frequent action taken by
      famous runner Clint Stevens.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      The fastest character for speedrunning in Super Mario
      Galaxy. Also a slippery and silly individual.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      This category of Super Mario Odyssey speedrunning
      involves runners attempting to capture enemies as
      little as physically possible. It is also a generic
      speedrunning category used in many different games.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      This speedrunner is the current world record holder
      for the “120 Star” category on speedrun.com.
    </clue>
  </category>

  <category name="BEFORE &amp; AFTER">
    <clue>Bowser’s royal name, followed by a standard shelled enemy.</clue>
    <clue>
      The title of the original Mario game for the Nintendo
      Entertainment System, followed by a mantra said among
      frat boys.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      The RPG series title highlighting the iconic plumber
      duo, followed by the green partner’s GameCube debut
      title.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      An obscure drawing game for the Super Nintendo,
      followed by the main tool used by Bowser Jr.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      The Nintendo Switch RPG collaboration with the Rayman
      franchise, followed by the most popular Spongebob
      Squarepants 3D platformer game (recently remade for
      current era consoles).
    </clue>
  </category>

  <category name="ENEMIES">
    <clue>
      This is the most standard ground-based enemy in the
      Mario universe: iconic for being grumpy, brown, and
      armless.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      A lead villain in Super Mario Sunshine, this character
      is famous for their flying vehicle and their infamous
      father.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      Famous for being shy around any hero, this enemy
      typically cannot be killed by traditional means.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      This magician often flies around and causes mischief
      for the heroes. He is also frequently portrayed as a
      right hand man to Bowser himself.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      Debuting in Super Mario 64 but being seen in many
      future games, this underwater creature is famous for
      scaring children and poking its long head out of holes
      in the wall.
    </clue>
  </category>

  <category name= "GAME WORLDS">
    <clue>
      Vast in size and sub-areas, this Super Mario
      Odyssey world features a pyramid that floats into
      the air.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      This hub world in Super Mario Sunshine features a
      tropical paradise with lively natives.
    </clue>
    <clue>
      There are this many worlds in the first Mario game
      for the Nintendo Entertainment System.
    </clue>
    <clue>This world is the first one accessible in Super Mario Galaxy.</clue>
    <clue>
      This world in Super Mario 64 was so beloved that
      it was recreated in Super Mario Galaxy 2. It also
      features a rather tall and skinny boss.
    </clue>
  </category>
</game>
